

EDUCATION

09/2007 - 06/2011

Complex of Mechanical
Schools No. 2 named after
Kazimierz Górski | Generała
Jana Skrzyneckiego 12, 30-363
Kraków
Car mechanic

09/2017 - 06/2020 Secondary school for adults Cossinus | Kremerowska 17, 31-130 Kraków

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Assertiveness and communication skills.
- Responsibleness and conscientiousness.
- High resistance to stress.
- Creativity.
- MS Office's package,
 Magento, SAP advanced.
- The basics of structural and object-oriented programming in C++.
- The basics of SQL, HTML and phpMyAdmin.
- Regular of CSS.
- English -B1/B2 (still

Damian Cichy

- 607441196
- damiancichy91@gmail.com
- Jana Kurczaba 33/7, 30-868 Kraków

SUMMARY

At the moment I am Castorama's employee, where I perform a function as the technical consultant. In my private and work life I experienced many ups and downs, but some time ago I have started to fight for my better future and constantly I am setting new goals. I am self-confident, ambitious, punctual and willing to improve my competences on professional and interpersonal fields. In my job I would like to have decent earnings, possibilities to improve myself and be fulfilled. My major aim is to expand my knowledge on programming and find a job connected with IT. I am fully aware that in front of me is a long way, filled with hard-work. To quote Sokrates: "There is only one good, knowledge, and one evil, ignorance."

EXPERIENCE

03/2011 - 08/2011 **Ziemiańska Restaurant** | Kraków Bodyguard

- Support for video monitoring.
- Taking care of the safety of the company's customers and employees.
- Keeping security documentation.
- Protection of property against theft and burglary.

09/2011 - 12/2011

Ziemiańska Restaurant | Kraków Waiter

- Customer service in accordance with the standards of the premises.
- Cooperation with other kitchen's employees with orders realization.
- Accepting reservations (by phone and e-mail).
- Waiter services with conferences and special events.

learning).

- Good manners.
- Very good work's organization skill.
- License for handling devices in the IP category.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Google certificate "Basics of Internet Marketing".
- Microsoft Excel Excel from Beginner to Advanced.
- Sololearn certificate
 "Structural and object oriented programming in
 C++"
- Sololearn certificate "SQL databases"
- Complementary sales training.
- Professional and comprehensive service for individual clients.
- Responsibility of the seller and the guarantor for the quality of the goods sold complaint procedure.

INTERESTS

My interests are focusing on programming. At the moment, I am learning by myself, but I am going to University in the near future. In my free time, I am reading fantasy books, mainly. I am the great fan of J.R.R. Tolkien's and Dmitrij Glukhovsky's works. What makes me calm is film and classical music e.g. Two Steps from Hell, Hans Zimmer and Howard Shore. I am fond of independent movies, but I stay open-minded for the rest.

• Keeping the hall in order.

01/2012 - 10/2012 **Ziemiańska** Restaurant| Kraków

Bartender

- Taking care of the proper work of the premises.
- Keeping bar clean.
- Billing and service cash register.
- Opening and closing permises, in which settlement of revenues.
- · Cooperation with other waitress.
- Brewing and serving coctails and other drinks according to my ideas.
- Management a seven-person group.

11/2012 - 04/2015 Instal Kraków | Kraków Locksmith

- Installation steel elements.
- Operation of power tools, incl. cutters, grinders, drills.
- Keeping my workplace clean.
- Performing disassembly, assembly, locksmith and renovation works.
- · Repair and maintenance of machines.

05/2015 - 04/2016 Instal Kraków | Kraków

Welder

- Preparation of parts for assembly (deburring, threading, reaming, drilling) and evaluation of their quality.
- Welding of materials using the MAG method.
- Installation of various elements based on technical drawings.
- Service low, high storage trolleys and crane.

06/2016 - 09/2016 Żabka | Kraków Shop assistance

- Service Cash register.
- Aesthetic display of products.
- Picking up and unloading goods.
- · Work organization and deliveries planning.

09/2016 - 06/2019

Castorama Polska Sp. z.o.o | Kraków Sales Advisor in the Floor Covering Department

- Maintaining positive relations with customers and supplier.
- Comprehensive and professional customer service.
- Completing internet orders.
- Complaints and return processing.
- Picking up and unloading goods.
- Multiple database monitoring to track all inventory levels in a department.
- Participation in trainings and courses.
- Continuous expanding knowledge on sales products.
- Service low and high storage trolleys.

07/2019 - now

Castorama Polska Sp. z.o.o | Kraków Sales Advisor in the Sanitary Department

- Maintaining positive relations with customers and supplier.
- Comprehensive and professional customer service.
- Completing internet orders.
- Complaints and return processing.
- Picking up and unloading goods.
- Multiple database monitoring to track all inventory levels in a department.
- · Participation in trainings and courses.
- Continuous expanding knowledge on sales products.
- Service low and high storage trolleys.

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

- Manager and captain of an amateur volleyball team SKP Bartosz with whom I won 1st place in the international amateur volleyball tournament in Zlaté Moravce.
- Organization of many parties and volleyball matches.
- Activities for the Polish Association of Disabled People.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).